Vanessa Yu

Irvine CA, 92614 (626) 321-0522 vanessapyu@gmail.com LinkedIn vanessayu.com

UX/UI Designer with experience defining strategy built on a deep understanding of both users and business needs alike. Thrives on creating user experiences based on awareness in diversity for both the digital and real world.

EXPERIENCE

Centaurus Financial, Anaheim CA — Operations Associate

October 2018 - Present

- Provide complete and efficient delivery of information
- Streamline workflow for maximum productivity
- Collaborate with internal and external teams to ensure quality

Bruber Media Partners, Arcadia CA — Film Distribution Assistant

June 2018 - Ongoing

- Provide deep analysis, feedback, and management of screenplays
- Illustrated proposal deck for potential investors
- Iterated screenplays with viewers in mind

Composite Apps, Irvine CA — Project Coordinator

September 2017 - October 2018

- Maintain collaborative mindset with solutions-oriented growth
- Executing four project schedules, budget expenditures and hours
- Primary point of contact for clients, design, and development

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design Bootcamp, Irvine, CA

March 2019 - Present

University of California of Irvine, Irvine, CA

September 2013 - June 2017

B.A. in International Studies Emphasis in Business and Operations with Focus on Asia

PROJECTS

Chinese Association's Culture Night — *Culture Night Producer* 2016–2017

- Produced and supervised a cultural production show with a large team
- Reduced expenses by 25% compared to last year's budget while maintaining production quality

SKILLS

Low to High Fidelity Prototyping

Personas

Storyboard

Wireframe

User Research

Usability Testing

User Journeys

TOOLS

Adobe XD

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

InVision

CSS

HTML

Affinity Designer

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)
Mandarin (Native)